Brownie battered Blizzard. 300 calories,
44 g of protein for the entire pint.
Welcome back to my series where I
recreate Dairy Queen Blizzard flavors,
but lower in calories and higher in
protein. This is the brownie batter
[music] Blizzard. Let me show you how to
make it. We're starting off with a
variation of my brownie batter base.
This [music] one uses 10 g of cocoa
powder and 10 g of black cocoa powder.
So, kind of a hybrid between chocolate
and honey batter. Then we're going to
blend that up. Throw it in the freezer
for at least 16 hours. Take it out, run
under hot water, and then throw it in
your creamy on light ice cream set. Then
we're going to take it out and scrape
down the sides with a butter knife.
It'll look pretty crumbly, but as long
as the sides are starting to melt
slightly, you'll know it's ready to be
scraped. Then we'll throw it back in the
creamy. You'll see I use the mix-in
setting instead of the respin setting.
This is because I knew it was close to
being done and the mixin setting runs
for less time and at less speed [music]
than the respin setting. And then to
finish this pint off, we're grabbing an
Alpha Prime Bites protein brownie,
chopping it into bite-sized pieces, and
then throwing it on top to mix in by